Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
دعم المشرف شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
♪Fade like drifting clouds♪
♪تتلاشى مثل السحب المنجرفة♪
♪Half dream, half illusion♪
♪نصف حلم، ونصف وهم♪
♪Fated or fleeting♪
♪مقدر أو عابر♪
♪Spring breeze falls from my brow♪
♪نسائم الربيع تهب من جبهتي♪
♪Where to go, I do not know♪
♪أين أذهب، لا أعرف♪
♪I turn, and all is gone♪
♪أتحول، وكل شيء قد ذهب♪
♪Ask how deep the dust of love runs♪
♪اسأل عن مدى عمق غبار الحب♪
♪How strong longing grows♪
♪ما أشد الشوق الذي ينمو♪
♪I play till the final note♪
♪ألعب حتى النغمة الأخيرة♪
=In The Name of Loyalty=
=باسم الولاء=
=Episode 20=
=الحلقة 20=
My lord,
سيدي،
all generals have deployed their troops
لقد نشر جميع الجنرالات قواتهم
to search the city.
للبحث في المدينة.
I believe Shi Nan will be apprehended shortly.
أعتقد أن شي نان سيتم القبض عليه قريبًا.
They're already like fish in a barrel to me.
إنهم بالنسبة لي مثل السمك في برميل.
What a pity.
يا للأسف.
I couldn't kill Shi Nan myself yesterday.
لم أستطع قتل شي نان بنفسي بالأمس.
It seems that shoot from years ago
يبدو أن هذه الصورة من سنوات مضت
didn't teach him a lesson.
لم يعلمه درسا.
Your Majesty. Your Majesty.
جلالتك. جلالتك.
The Wardrobe Bureau just sent over a new garment.
لقد أرسل لنا مكتب خزانة الملابس للتو ثوبًا جديدًا.
They request your inspection.
يطلبون منك التفتيش.
Is this the time
هل هذا هو الوقت
to try new garments?
لتجربة ملابس جديدة؟
Your Majesty, don't get angry.
جلالتك لا تغضب.
But the eunuch who delivered the garment
ولكن الخصي الذي سلم الثوب
looked unfamiliar.
بدا غير مألوف.
He left a cryptic message.
لقد ترك رسالة غامضة.
This is what His Majesty needs most.
وهذا ما يحتاجه جلالته أكثر من أي شيء آخر.
Open it to understand.
افتحه لفهمه.
(Get antidote at Eternal Light Temple)
(احصل على الترياق في معبد النور الأبدي)
Your Majesty.
جلالتك.
It's me.
هذا أنا.
You sent the garment?
هل أرسلت الثوب؟
Cheng Ge is in danger now. Give me the antidote.
تشنغ جي في خطر الآن. أعطني الترياق.
I told you to come.
لقد قلت لك أن تأتي.
You'll get it naturally.
ستحصل عليه بشكل طبيعي.
Wanted posters of you can be seen everywhere.
يمكنك رؤية الملصقات المطلوبة لك في كل مكان.
It's relatively safe here.
إنه آمن نسبيا هنا.
Remember this.
تذكر هذا.
Don't wander about.
لا تتجول.
I'll regularly send people to provide food to you.
سأرسل أشخاصًا بانتظام لتزويدك بالطعام.
Don't think I'll forgive you for this.
لا أعتقد أنني سأسامحك على هذا.
Nan.
في.
I know
أنا أعرف
you care for the realm.
أنت تهتم بالمملكة.
All these years,
كل هذه السنوات،
I've failed you deeply.
لقد خذلتك بشدة.
Too many died unjustly because of me.
لقد مات الكثيرون ظلماً بسببي.
But this was never my intention.
ولكن هذا لم يكن قصدي أبدًا.
After all that's happened,
بعد كل ما حدث،
I can't bear losing anyone else.
لا أستطيع أن أتحمل فقدان أي شخص آخر.
Hurry. Don't delay.
اسرع، لا تتأخر.
Nan.
في.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
Give Cheng Ge this message.
أعطي تشنغ جي هذه الرسالة.
I've wronged her all these years.
لقد ظلمتها كل هذه السنوات.
I was wrong.
لقد كنت مخطئا.
What does it say?
ماذا يقول؟
(Notice)
(يلاحظ)
Cheng Ge.
تشنغ قه.
C-Cheng Ge.
ج-تشنغ قه.
Your Grace,
صاحب السمو،
the Prince Regent is here.
الأمير الوصي هنا.
Zhiying,
تشي ينغ،
the envoys heard you favor kites.
سمع المبعوثون أنك تفضل الطائرات الورقية.
So they brought a lot,
لقد أحضروا الكثير،
all in styles you'd appreciate.
كل ذلك بالأنماط التي ترغب بها.
Take a look.
خذ نظرة.
My lord,
سيدي،
I've ordered a citywide hunt for Shi Nan.
لقد أمرت بمطاردة على مستوى المدينة لشي نان.
He remains at large.
ولا يزال طليقا.
Zhiying,
تشي ينغ،
I'll leave these here.
سأتركهم هنا.
I'm truly full.
أنا ممتلئة حقا.
Eat more
تناول المزيد
and recover faster.
والتعافي بشكل أسرع.
By the way,
بالمناسبة،
where did you
أين كنت؟
get the antidote?
احصل على الترياق؟
Of course, it's from Shi Nan.
بالطبع، إنه من شي نان.
He also entrusted me with words for you.
لقد أوكل إليّ أيضًا كلمات لك.
What words?
ما الكلمات؟
He said
قال
he's wronged you all these years
لقد ظلمك كل هذه السنوات
and he was wrong.
وكان مخطئا.
It seems
يبدو أنه
you still can't forgive him.
لا تزال غير قادر على مسامحته.
Forgive him?
سامحه؟
Must I forgive him?
هل يجب علي أن أسامحه؟
I once thought
لقد اعتقدت ذات مرة
he was the only one
لقد كان الوحيد
I could trust in this world.
أستطيع أن أثق في هذا العالم.
But I never thought
ولكنني لم افكر ابدا
in his eyes,
في عينيه،
I was just a blade,
لقد كنت مجرد شفرة،
a pawn,
بيدق
and a sacrifice.
وتضحية.
My pain he caused
الألم الذي سببه لي
was a calculated
كان محسوبا
and deliberate choice.
والاختيار المتعمد.
He never treated me with sincerity.
لم يعاملني بصدق أبدًا.
Then
ثم
why did you take that stab for him?
لماذا قمت بهذه الطعنة من أجله؟
Because...
لأن...
Because he is important to you.
لأنه مهم بالنسبة لك.
I don't want you to lose anyone else.
لا أريدك أن تخسر أي شخص آخر.
From this moment onward,
من هذه اللحظة فصاعدا،
you are the most important person to me.
أنت الشخص الأكثر أهمية بالنسبة لي.
What do you think?
ماذا تعتقد؟
Does it look good?
هل يبدو جيدا؟
This is...
هذا هو...
This symbolizes that we must
وهذا يرمز إلى أنه يجب علينا
work in unison
العمل في انسجام
and fight as one.
وقاتلوا كواحد.
Come on. Let me put it on for you.
هيا، دعني أضعه لك.
Tell me
أخبرني
if this counts as our love token.
إذا كان هذا يعد رمزًا لمحبتنا.
Is that all you've got to offer me?
هل هذا كل ما لديك لتقدمه لي؟
Then it doesn't count.
إذن لا يهم.
Childish.
طفولي.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
Where to?
إلى أين؟
To the palace.
الى القصر.
Taking him to the palace?
أخذه إلى القصر؟
Right now,
الآن،
Gao Ji thinks my brother
غاو جي يعتقد أن أخي
hates my guts.
يكره أحشائي.
He'd never believe I'd
لن يصدق أبدًا أنني سأفعل ذلك
bring him to the palace.
أحضره إلى القصر.
That's called hiding in plain sight.
هذا ما يسمى بالاختباء أمام أعيننا.
♪Without fate, this dream would fade♪
♪بدون القدر، هذا الحلم سوف يتلاشى♪
♪Without you, my life would quietly end♪
♪بدونك، حياتي ستنتهي بهدوء♪
♪Fade like drifting clouds♪
♪تتلاشى مثل السحب المنجرفة♪
♪Half dream, half illusion♪
♪نصف حلم، ونصف وهم♪
♪Fated or fleeting♪
♪مقدر أو عابر♪
♪Spring breeze falls from my brow♪
♪نسائم الربيع تهب من جبهتي♪
♪Where to go, I do not know♪
♪أين أذهب، لا أعرف♪
♪I turn, and all is gone♪
♪أتحول، وكل شيء قد ذهب♪
♪Ask how deep the dust of love runs♪
♪اسأل عن مدى عمق غبار الحب♪
♪How strong longing grows♪
♪ما أشد الشوق الذي ينمو♪
♪I play till the final note♪
♪ألعب حتى النغمة الأخيرة♪
♪Let fate cut like a blade♪
♪دع القدر يقطع مثل الشفرة♪
♪I bid you one last farewell♪
♪أقول لك وداعا أخيرا♪
♪I know not love's emptiness nor hatred's pain♪
♪لا أعرف فراغ الحب ولا ألم الكراهية♪
♪When we meet again, the snow will melt away♪
♪عندما نلتقي مرة أخرى، سوف يذوب الثلج♪
♪One vow, so deep in love♪
♪عهد واحد، عميق في الحب♪
♪I'd give my life for it♪
♪سأعطي حياتي من أجله♪